[
    {
      "question": "übertragen",
      "correctAnswer": "aktarmak",
      "answer" :["abartmak","bakmak", "kusmak"]

    },
    {
        "question": "lösen",
        "correctAnswer": "cözmek",
        "answer" :["kaybetnek","silmek", "bakmak"]

  
      },
      {
        "question": "fragen",
        "correctAnswer": "sormak",
        "answer" :["cevaplamak","acmak", "kacmak"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "lesen",
        "correctAnswer": "okumak",
        "answer" :["konusmak","seslenmek", "bagirmak"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "enschieden",
        "correctAnswer": "karar vermek",
        "answer" :["denemek","secmek", "toplamak"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "bringen",
        "correctAnswer": "getirmek",
        "answer" :["satin almak","almak", "birakmak"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "hören",
        "correctAnswer": "duymak",
        "answer" :["okumak","yemek", "gelmek"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "kaufen",
        "correctAnswer": "satin almak",
        "answer" :["almak","satmak", "getirmek"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "sitzen",
        "correctAnswer": "oturmak",
        "answer" :["ayakta durmak","yatmak", "bakmak"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "beobachten",
        "correctAnswer": "gözlemlemek",
        "answer" :["basarmak","bakmak", "bagirmak"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "antworten",
        "correctAnswer": "cevaplamak",
        "answer" :["sormak","bulmak", "okumak"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "arbeiten",
        "correctAnswer": "calismak",
        "answer" :["anlamak","yakinmak", "düsünmek"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "rennen",
        "correctAnswer": "kosmak",
        "answer" :["dusmek","yanmak", "almak"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "sprechen",
        "correctAnswer": "konusmak",
        "answer" :["yazmak","okumak", "dinlemek"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "schreiben",
        "correctAnswer": "yazmak",
        "answer" :["konusmak","tirmanmak", "oynamak"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "denken",
        "correctAnswer": "düsünmek",
        "answer" :["tesekkür etmek","beklemek", "sormak"]
  
      }
  ]